http://www.agc.org/privacy-policy

Last Modified: August 26, 2020
AGC has created this policy statement to help users of this website (“Website”) understand how we collect, use, and protect information about them. The term "user" in this policy statement refers to visitors of the Website. The term "collected information" refers specifically to information collected from the Website.
Information Collected
For each visitor to this Website, we collect the user's IP address and certain information about the user's equipment (e.g., type of browser, screen resolution, support for Java). We do not automatically record other user-specific, personal information. Such personal information (e.g., email address, telephone number, photographic image) is recorded only when volunteered by the user (e.g., when a user registers for a meeting, purchases a product, responds to a survey, or completes or revises a user profile). Highly sensitive personal information, like credit card, Social Security number, passport, biometric data, and bank account numbers, that you may provide in relation to a transaction with AGC is never recorded by or stored in AGC’s IT systems.
Technologies used to gather information
AGC employs several technologies including but not limited to cookies, web beacons, browser cache technologies, locally stored objects, statistical identifiers, clear gifs, embedded scripts and similar means.
Use of Collected Information
AGC's primary objective in collecting user information is to provide superior services and benefits to members and customers. In furtherance of that objective, AGC may use information we collect from you to:  provide you with services, products, resources, events, surveys, awards, support, and benefits, and information about same; provide advertisements that are more likely to be of interest to you; measure and improve our services and operations (including IT systems); protect our legal rights, contractual rights, and the safety, privacy, and security of other users and the public; send advocacy communications and voter information; and to comply with laws and requests from public and government authorities. Collected user-specific information is normally incorporated into AGC's general database of members and other contacts. While AGC does not sell user-specific data to third parties solely for AGC’s commercial gain, AGC does share information about members and other contacts in that database with third parties from time to time, such as when we provide attendees of an AGC event with a registrants list or share committee rosters with members and chapters. Sometimes, the sharing may be partially for commercial purposes, such as when we provide membership lists (possibly including contact information) to companies with which AGC has an established business relationship (such as “affinity partners” so that they may directly market to AGC members about the products or services they offer at an AGC-member discount). In some cases, user information is automatically shared with third parties by virtue of AGC’s use third-party-provided technology, such as meeting registration software. AGC makes efforts to prevent unaffiliated third parties from using your information for AGC-unauthorized purposes but cannot control, and is not responsible for, the privacy practices or other conduct of such parties.
Access to Personal Information
Users can access and revise most of the collected information about them by using the Change My Profile feature at www.agc.org/myaccount. Additional information may be attainable from AGC's Membership Department by email at membership@agc.org or by telephone at (703) 548–3118.
Opportunity to Opt-Out
Because collected information volunteered by the user is automatically stored in AGC's member and contacts database along with information collected by means other than this site, it is not possible to specifically opt out from the use of collected information. However, users may submit a request to limit marketing or to avoid specific modes of communication (e.g., mail, fax, email) or specific AGC publications (e.g., Constructor magazine, News & Views newsletter) by contacting the AGC Membership Department by email at membership@agc.org or by telephone at (703) 548–3118.
In addition to this, users can decline the use of non-essential cookies during their browsing session. Non-essential cookies are those commonly used for advertising. Essential cookies are those that allow basic functionality, like maintaining a shopping cart. AGC provides this option during a user’s first visit to our website.
Security
This site and the servers that store collected information have industry–standard security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under AGC's control. Please note, however, that no security system is 100% secure. Authentic website pages requesting credit card information will be secure web pages, and sensitive data will be encrypted for transmission. Absent user consent, AGC does not knowingly share credit card numbers with third parties except to the extent necessary for, and incidental to, the purposes for which the user supplied the information.
Links to Other Web Sites
This site contains links to other websites, some of which may look similar to this site and appear to be a part of this site but which may be hosted by third parties. In some cases, those third parties may also gather user data and may have a privacy policy different from AGC’s. AGC is not responsible for the privacy practices, content, or security of such sites or third parties.
International Users
OUR OPERATIONS ARE CONDUCTED WITHIN THE UNITED STATES.  OUR SERVICES ARE INTENDED FOR USE BY RESIDENTS OF, OR VISITORS IN, THE UNITED STATES ONLY.  OUR SERVICES ARE NOT INTENDED FOR USE OUTSIDE OF THE UNITED STATES.  If you access our website from outside of the United States, your connection may be through and to servers located in your country or in the United States, or even in other countries where our service providers may process data.  Any personal information you provide may be processed and maintained in the United States on servers and/or other network systems operated by us or for our benefit.  Regardless of where you reside, your use of our website constitutes your affirmative consent to have your personal information transferred, processed and stored in the United States, and to allow us to use and collect your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. IF THE JURISDICTION IN WHICH YOU ARE LOCATED OR YOUR COUNTRY OF ORIGIN HAS LAWS OR REGULATIONS WHICH REQUIRE THAT YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION BE RECEIVED USED, SAVED, TRANSFERRED AND/OR OTHERWISE HANDLED IN A MANNER DIFFERENT THAN AS STATED IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY, THEN YOU ARE NOT AUTHORIZED TO UTILIZE OUR WEBSITE OR ANY SERVICES WE MAY PROVIDE. IF YOU ACCESS OUR SERVICES FROM AND/OR RESIDE OUTSIDE OF THE UNITED STATES, YOUR INFORMATION MAY BE STORED, TRANSMITTED AND SHARED IN ACCORDANCE WITH U.S. PRIVACY AND DATA PROTECTION LAWS, WHICH MAY NOT BE EQUIVALENT TO THOSE IN EFFECT IN YOUR COUNTRY. YOU EXPRESSLY AGREE THAT YOU WILL NOT USE OUR WEBSITE OR ANY OF OUR SERVICES WITH ANY EXPECTATION OF GREATER PRIVACY RIGHTS THAN THOSE TO WHICH YOU HAVE EXPRESSLY AGREED AS STATED IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY.
Changes to Policy and Deviation from Policy
AGC reserves the right to revise this policy and to use collected information for uses not previously disclosed without prior notice and at any time. If policy changes are made, a revised policy will be posted on this page. If you are concerned about changes to this policy, deviations from this policy, or the use of collected information, please contact privacy@agc.org.
Contractor Type:
Utility
Federal/Heavy
Highway
Building
About AGC
The Associated General Contractors of America (AGC) is the leading association for the construction industry. AGC represents more than 27,000 firms, including over 6,500 of America’s leading general contractors, and over 9,000 specialty-contracting firms. More than 10,500 service providers and suppliers are also associated with AGC, all through a nationwide network of chapters.
Learn More
Industry Priorities
Advocacy
Infrastructure
Safety & Health
Workforce Development
Contracts & Law
Labor & HR
The Associated General Contractors of America, Inc.
(AGC) of America, Inc. All rights reserved.
